mailburn.com 2015-03-14

# Mailburn - iPhone email client for Gmail with chat like conversations, email tracking and swipe gestures for business productivity

**The security of your data is paramount to us.**

Mailburn Inc. (later “Mailburn”, “We”, “Us”) Privacy Policy describes our policy on collecting, storing and using your data and personal information within Mailburn application and services. This Privacy Policy is limited to the data stored and handled directly within Mailburn. Other third party applications connected to Mailburn usually have their own privacy policies, and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

## What information do we collect and why?

**Remember, your privacy is extremely important to us**. No person at Mailburn will ever read any of your email or data except in the specific, narrow circumstances described in this Privacy Policy. Mailburn has various security measures to protect your email and data from unauthorized disclosure. We will not ask for your email password unless we need it to provide our service to you. 

Some of the data goes through Mailburn service so that we can provide you with best email experience. However we don't store any emails or attachments permanently on our servers. We might securely store them temporarily to analyze, index and speed up deliver of emails. 

Such data might be:

  * Contact details and email address
  * Your contact book
  * Incoming and outgoing emails and attachments (strictly for analysis or betterment of Mailburn service).
  * Location, browser cookies, IP address
  * Any other data manually added to our system

## Technical Support

If you encounter problems with your Mailburn experience, you may contact our technical support. For us to provide support, we need your name, email address, and app logs. Occasionally, problems may arise that require access to your account. We will never ask for access to your account unless such access is absolutely necessary to address an issue with your Mailburn experience. If you provide us with express consent, we may access your account to troubleshoot issues. We grant such access only to certain Mailburn people and only in very limited circumstances with your knowledge and consent. 

## Website Visitor Information

When you visit Mailburn website, we collect some basic information about your visit, such as your location, IP address, browser type, and the website that referred you to ours. We use this information for purposes of analyzing, marketing, and improving the Mailburn service. 

## Does Mailburn share my information with third parties?

We don't do this kind of things. Your email and associated data belong to you or, if it is a work account, to your employer. We will not share any of that with third parties except in the following narrow circumstances:

  * If the owner of the account expressly authorizes disclosure to a third party, we may disclose the information as authorized.
  * If your email account is a work account that belongs to your employer, they have the right to access and control your account, including its contents.
  * If we believe in good faith that we are legally required to disclose information to comply with laws or to respond to lawful demands, we may do so.
  * If we sell or reorganize all or part of our business, we may need to disclose user information to a third party who acquires our assets, as permitted by law.

## Can I delete my account?

You can delete your account by emailing [support@mailburn.com](mailto:support@mailburn.com). We will delete your account, including your emails and associated data, as soon as we can, and will only retain information as required by law. 

## Does Mailburn offer services to children?

No. Mailburn users must not be under the age of 13. We do not target any portion of our service to children under the age of 13, and in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we will delete any accounts or data of users that we believe to be under the age of 13. 

## What happens if Mailburn changes this Privacy Policy?

Any information that is collected is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise our privacy policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on the service or by sending you an email or other notification, and we will indicate when such changes will become effective. By continuing to access or use the Mailburn service after those changes become effective, you are agreeing to be bound by the revised policy.
